

PROFILE

I am a driven data engineer and robotics developer. Programming and working with computers in general has been a passion for quite some time.

In love with automation and minimizing repetitive work, which is why I'm able to focus on efficient & application-oriented learning, developing and problem solving.

Switching views, working on agile projects and changing approaches often motivate me to study new topics, tackle hard challenges and deliver results.

BIRTHDATE

11 januari 2000

ADDRESS

Houthalen-Helchteren, Belgium

PHONE NUMBER

+32486539354

MAILING ADDRESS

kobethuwis26@gmail.com

GITHUB PORTFOLIO LINKEDIN

KOBE THUWIS

WORK EXPERIENCE

InfoFarm: Data Consultant 2021 - Present

Lineas Data Squad

Lineas is the largest private rail freight operator in Europe. I develop and setup Kubernetes clusters, AWS data pools and NiFi data flows using Terraform and custom scripts, in order to provide a central data storage and management platform.

ANPR Big Data Platform

The ANPR Big Data Platform is a scalable and extensible platform for collecting, storing and aggregating ANPR data. My task within the project is to construct a big data lake using AWS and make the data usable for analysis, reporting and future processing.

PXL Smart ICT: Research & Development Intern 2021

ArtiFISHal Intelligence is a twofold project, primarily consisting of scenes made in Unity which illustrate several reinforcement learning techniques. Secondly, the project contains a simulation of a marine ecosystem which uses an open-ended algorithm, NEAT.

Chiro Meulenberg: Head Monitor 2018 - Present

Strandbal: Event Manager 2018 - Present

Youth Council Member 2019 - Present

EDUCATION

Amazon Web Services 2021

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

Hogeschool PXL 2018 - 2021

Bachelor Applied Information Technology (AI & Robotics)

Kindsheid Jesu 2012 - 2018

High school diploma in Maths & Sciences